<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Entries>
  <Entry title="JavaScript shenanigans 2" created="March 28th, 2008">New version of my JavaScript editor written in .NET. Still no syntax highlighting, but now there are "tabbed documents". Okay, okay, so they are just buttons that change which script is set in the textbox, but it's close enough. Oh, also an eval line (just below the editor window). Basically, you can write a script and then execute a single line as if it were a part of the script (without it being part of the script) and see what its return value would be. Yeah, sort of like interactive mode in Pythong or Ruby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="RnD/DotNET/JSRE/eBang1.1b.zip"&gt;&lt;img src="RnD/DotNET/JSRE/screen2.png" alt="screenshot" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry title="JavaScript shenanigans" created="March 22nd, 2008">Just finished up v1.0 of a JavaScript editor written in .NET. There isn't any syntax highlighting, but code is actually &lt;i&gt;compiled&lt;/i&gt; on the fly. As far as features, you should have access to just about anything you would want in .NET (I haven't included every assembly, but the most important stuff is there). There are also simplistic implementations of the &lt;b&gt;print&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;println&lt;/b&gt;, and &lt;b&gt;alert&lt;/b&gt; functions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="RnD/DotNET/JSRE/jsre1.0b.zip"&gt;&lt;img src="RnD/DotNET/JSRE/screen.png" alt="screenshot" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry title="Other Illusionists?" created="April 30th, 2006">I recently stumbled upon a researcher at Northwestern Univeristy by the name of &lt;a href="http://www.cs.northwestern.edu/~holger/"&gt;Holger Winnemoeller&lt;/a&gt;. He has done some research in NPR Rendering, mostly optimizing existing NPR techniques. His &lt;a href="http://www.cs.northwestern.edu/~holger/WWWMasters/masters_thesis_proposal.html"&gt;Master's Thesis Proposal&lt;/a&gt; talked about using optical illusions, in much the same way that I used them for my research project. I've since been in contact with Holger, he seems like a pretty interesting guy.</Entry>
  <Entry title="PocketDice" created="March 21st, 2006">PocketDice for PocketPC is a little convenience program for anyone that does anything with dice. I play a number of games that can use any number of dice, so having this program is very handy. No more dice skittering all over everywhere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="RnD/PocketPC/PocketDice/dice.png" alt="PocketDice" /&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry title="PocketEdit" created="January 17th, 2006">PocketEdit for PocketPC is finished.
    Unfortunately, the clipboard is not supported in the .NET Compact
    Framework v1.0, so your clipboard data will not be available to other
    applications.&lt;br /&gt;
    I find PocketEdit to be a very handy application for editting text files. Windows Mobile 2003 does not ship with a plain text editor, which can be quite bothersome at times. With PocketEdit, I can edit HTML files while on the go, and quickly view them in Pocket IE. OH LOOK! A screeny!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="RnD/PocketPC/PocketEdit/pe1.PNG" alt="PocketEdit" /&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry title="RunningTracker" created="January 16th, 2006">
    I've put the finishing touches on the RunningTracker app for .NET Compact Framework capable PocketPC PDAs. Use Check out the screenies!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="RnD/PocketPC/RunningTracker/rt1.PNG" alt="RunTrack" /&gt;&lt;img src="RnD/PocketPC/RunningTracker/rt2.PNG" alt="RunTrack" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="RnD/PocketPC/RunningTracker/rt3.PNG" alt="RunTrack" /&gt;&lt;img src="RnD/PocketPC/RunningTracker/rt4.PNG" alt="RunTrack" /&gt;</Entry>
</Entries>
